Welcome. Today we're demonstrating Zurn Elkay Competitive Intelligence System
for Zurn Elkay Water Solutions. The challenge: CI analysts spend weeks manually
gathering data, each BU does CI differently making roll-ups difficult, and
coordinated competitor moves across parent companies like Watts are missed.
Traditional approaches take 4-6 weeks per quarterly CI cycle. With our AI agent
approach, we deliver in hours with automated data gathering and human review.
Architecture Overview
We ask: "Show me how the Zurn Elkay CI system is structured." The
zurnelkay_ci_orchestrator_agent agent processes this request.
Single BU Deep Dive — Run Drains quarterly analysis. We ask: "Run a quarterly
competitive intelligence analysis for the Drains business unit." The
zurnelkay_drains_ci_agent agent processes this request.
Parent Company Coordination — Check Watts across Drains. We ask: "Check for
coordinated moves by Watts Water Technologies across their drain brands." The
zurnelkay_drains_ci_agent agent processes this request.
BU Differentiation
We ask: "Show how each BU agent is specialized. What does the Wilkins agent
track for digital innovation?" The zurnelkay_wilkins_ci_agent agent processes
this request.
Competitor Deep Dive — Analyze Watts in Wilkins category. We ask: "Give me a
deep analysis of Watts as a competitor in the Wilkins space." The
zurnelkay_wilkins_ci_agent agent processes this request.
Source Transparency — Drinking Water certifications. We ask: "Show me NSF
certification changes in the Drinking Water category with full source
attribution." The zurnelkay_drinking_water_ci_agent agent processes this
request.
Healthcare Focus — Sinks competitive landscape. We ask: "What healthcare
innovations are happening in the Sinks competitive space?" The
zurnelkay_sinks_ci_agent agent processes this request.
Platform Competition — Commercial Brass strategic shift. We ask: "What platform
launches are happening in Commercial Brass?" The
zurnelkay_commercial_brass_ci_agent agent processes this request.
Enterprise Intelligence
We ask: "Now show me the cross-BU synthesis — what patterns emerge across all
five business units?" The zurnelkay_crossbu_synthesizer_agent agent processes
this request.
Executive Briefing — CEO-ready output. We ask: "Generate the executive briefing
for the quarterly strategy review." The zurnelkay_crossbu_synthesizer_agent
agent processes this request.
System Management — Orchestrator health check. We ask: "Run a system health
check on the entire CI agent swarm." The zurnelkay_ci_orchestrator_agent agent
processes this request.
That concludes our Zurn Elkay Competitive Intelligence System demonstration.
Key takeaway: Purpose-built multi-agent CI system with parent company
coordination tracking, confidence calibration, and CEO-ready executive
briefings. Thank you for watching.